## I PUTU ADI BAWA

COOK/IT/ADMIN

Click This Link To Check My Portfolio Website





#### PROFILE

Hello, My Name is I PUTU ADI BAWA I'm Japanese Food Maker with totally 4 years experience & Have Experience in Office. I Live in Badung Bali

Take your time, check my resume, see my skil -ls, some of my work. my experience and whe -n you are ready to drop me a message

#### CONTACT

- Perum Sambada Asri Mengwi Badung
- +62 822 577 668 66
- 🕽 github/adiko-dot
- C click this link
- in linkein/tuadi

#### SKILLS

JAPANESES COOK

WESBITE DESIGN

GRAPHIC DESIGN

OFFICE SOFTWARE

#### INTERESTS

sports, philosophy, networking, books, tecnology, japanese culture, mathematics, healthy food, chess.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### nov2019 - nov2020 / Cook Japanese - ABURI SUSHI

Open shift, take a raw material from supplier, checking stock items, making soup chicken , soup dashi, miso soup, chicken teriyaki, beef slice for donburi items, ongseng egg, making condiment ramen, sauce donburi, sauce shoyu, sauce udon,egg condiment for noodles

#### may2019 - oct2019 / Cook Japanese - 7 TORI SAMURAI SUNSET

Open shift, take a raw material from supplier, prepare exchange money, checking stock items, making soup chicken ramen, chicken karaage , chicken katsu & chassu, making condiment ramen making ramen noddles with a machine, taking order, closing shift, checking sold items, make a list order raw material.

#### nov2016 - sept2017 / Head Stall - MAXX KITCHEN LIPPO

Open shift, take a raw material from supplier, prepare exchange money, checking stock items, making chicken karaage , chicken katsu & chassu, making condiment takoyaki, omurice, bento set, tepanyaki, taking order & input POS, closing shift, checking sold items, maké a list order raw material.

#### **HEADSTALL**

Make purchase order, inventory 1 week & 1 month, stock opname daily check, closing shift input selling to system, check cost for 1 month, make daily shifting staff.

#### sept2016 - nov2016 / Cook Japanese - MAD RONNIN

Open shift, take a raw material from supplier, prepare chicken soup & tongkotsu soup, condiment ramen, gyoza, karaage, chicken chasuu, pork chassu.

#### feb2016 - sept2016 / Cook Japanese - 7 TORI SAMURAI SUNSET

Open shift, take a raw material from supplier, prepare exchange money, checking stock items, making soup chicken ramen, chicken karaage , chicken katsu & chassu, making condiment ramen making ramen noddles with a machine, taking order, closing shift, checking sold items, make a list order raw material.

#### EDUCATION

**2012 - 2015 / SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL** SMK PGRI 3 DENPASAR

2009 - 2012/ JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL SMP PGRI 3 DENPASAR

2005 - 2009 / ELEMNTARY SCHOOL SDPN TULANGAMPIANG DENPASAR

LANGUAGES

Indonesian **English** 

## **PUTU ADI BAWA**

COOK/IT/ADMIN

Click This Link To Check My Portfolio Website



Dear Sir/Madam,

I would like to take this opportunity to apply for a position in your company.

My name is I PUTU ADI BAWA, 23 Years Old. I would like to expand my experience in the hospitality industry. Mypersonality as a hard worker & fast leaner is the type of person that would bring benefit to your company i enclose my curriculum vitae which will give details of my qualifications, work history.

Nama : I Putu Adi Bawa

Place/Date of Birth : Denpasar, 02 march 1997

: Puspa Resti Street Perum Sambadaasri Blok 1 No. 6 Penarungan Mengwi **Address** 

Marital Status : Single

: Senior High School **Last Education** 

**Nationality** : INDONESIAN Religion : HINDU BUDDHA

No Phone : +62 822 577 668 66

Height/Weight : 175cm / 86kg

: iputuadibawa@gmail.com **Fmail** 

I am looking forward to hearing you soon and to being given the opportunity of a interview. Your Attention is highly appreciated. Thank You

# SERTIFIKAT PENYELESAIAN

Sertifikat ini menyatakan bahwa

## I Putu Adi Bawa

telah berhasil menyelesaikan

4 Study dan 1 Latihan pada

## **Kursus PHP**

Kursus ini mencakup dasar-dasar PHP untuk pengembangan web.

01/12/2020

Sertifikat ini telah di verifikasi oleh Masa Kato Founder & CEO Progate





# CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION

This is to certify that

## I Putu Adi Bawa

successfully completed the

## Path Pengembangan Web(Node.js)

on Progate, an online platform for learning programming.

 $December\ 5th\ 2020$ 

9 Checkpoints completed

Certificate URL: progate.com/path\_certificate/372fae62qkv6ti

Masa Kato

Cerfitication verified by Masa Kato Founder & CEO of Progate



# SERTIFIKAT PENYELESAIAN

Sertifikat ini menyatakan bahwa

## I Putu Adi Bawa

telah berhasil menyelesaikan

1 Study pada

## **Kursus Sass**

Kursus ini mencakup dasar-dasar Sass.

02/12/2020

Sertifikat ini telah di verifikasi oleh Masa Kato Founder & CEO Progate



# SERTIFIKAT PENYELESAIAN

Sertifikat ini menyatakan bahwa

## I Putu Adi Bawa

telah berhasil menyelesaikan

4 Study dan 3 Latihan pada

## **Kursus HTML & CSS**

Kursus ini mencakup fundamental HTML & CSS.

25/11/2020

Sertifikat ini telah di verifikasi oleh Masa Kato Founder & CEO Progate





# CERTIFICATE of Completion

is presented to

## I PUTU ADI BAWA

Course

Completion Date

**Data Science Python** 

15-12-2020

Authorized code

Course Content Provider

14122020-251438-KP-BABA

Issued by

Siti Rohmah

Director of babastudio.com



72ZD28056ZYW

Diberikan kepada

### I Putu Adi Bawa

Atas kelulusannya pada kelas

Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web

06 November 2020

Narenda Wicaksono

Chief Executive Officer Dicoding Indonesia SERTIFIKAT KOMPETENSI





Verifikasi Sertifikat

dicoding.com/certificates/72ZD28056ZYW Berlaku hingga 06 November 2023



QLZ98Q377X5D

Diberikan kepada

#### I Putu Adi Bawa

Atas kelulusannya pada kelas

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Android untuk Pemula

23 Agustus 2019

Narenda Wicaksono

Chief Executive Officer Dicoding Indonesia







Verifikasi Sertifikat

dicoding.com/certificates/QLZ98Q377X5D Berlaku hingga 23 Agustus 2022